[HUMMING]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
You don't have to do that.
We've got staff for it.
Come on.
Consider it one of my freebies
for you.
What's that?
I was going to send it
to the laundry.
The laundry? I'll do it!
- Give it to me!
- No.
Come on. Don't be shy.
- Give it to me.
- No, it's fine.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
What's this?
[CLEARS THROAT]
A stain?
I'll wash it for you.
Don't be shy.
This'll be easy.
You don't have to adjust
for me, okay?
I'm only here for the company.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
For the company.
Didn't you say...
we have to make everyone
believe...
that we're serious?
So...
I'm one hundred percent
committed.
Here.
- What's this?
- Your lunch.
Go on, it's time for work.
Go on.
It's good. Go on.
Get to work!
You're so fussy.
Dear, can I ask you something?
I've been seeing all this
stuff online about...
DNA tests.
Did the attorney have you
take one?
A DNA test?
Ma...
How could that happen?
The Roces are already
at the bottom
of the West Philippine Sea.
- Oh, right.
- Why'd you ask, Ma?
Nothing.
It just crossed my mind.
I'll wash this first, Ma.
- So many stains!
- Okay, go ahead.
Do a good job, okay?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Good morning, sir!
[JUNE] Don't skip your meals
at work.
Take care, Papa Ping.
Love, Baby Bulol.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Your girlfriend's
so sweet, boss.
It's been a while since
I've seen you smile like that.
[ENGINE STARTING]
Must be nice!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]